{
    "Category0" : {
      "question0": {
        "question": "Is shooting in a competition a olympic sport?",
        "choice1": "yes",
        "choice2": "no",
        "choice3": "no, but was for a brief moment",
        "choice4": "yes, but soon will not be",
        "answer": "1"
      },
        "question1" : {
            "question" : "Will the 2020 Olympics in Tokyo continue?",
            "choice1" : "yes",
            "choice2" : "no",
            "choice3" : "yes but in 2021 cause of the corona virus",
            "choice4" : "I dont know nor care",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question2" : {
            "question" : "Which sport is most popular in India?",
            "choice1" : "soccer",
            "choice2" : "baseball",
            "choice3" : "basketball",
            "choice4" : "cricket",
            "answer" : "4"
        },
        "question3" : {
            "question" : "Who won the Superbowl in 2020?",
            "choice1" : "Kansas City chiefs",
            "choice2" : "New England Patriots",
            "choice3" : "Green Bay Packers",
            "choice4" : "Baltimore Reavens",
            "answer" : "1"
        },
        "question4" : {
            "question" : "Where is American football derrived from?",
            "choice1" : "rugby",
            "choice2" : "football",
            "choice3" : "Golf",
            "choice4" : "Basketball",
            "answer" : "1"
        }
    },

    "Category1" : {
        "question0" : {
            "question" : "Whats the original name of Istanbul?",
            "choice1" : "Istanbul",
            "choice2" : "Constantinopel",
            "choice3" : "Byzantium",
            "choice4" : "Muraz",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question1" : {
            "question" : "How big was the British empire at its height?",
            "choice1" : "population 20% and land area  30%",
            "choice2" : "population and land area nearly a quatre of the world",
            "choice3" : "population 40 % land area 20%",
            "choice4" : "population 20% land area 40%",
            "answer" : "2"
        },
        "question2" : {
            "question" : "In the greek mythos who gave fire to man?",
            "choice1" : "Prometheus",
            "choice2" : "Zeus",
            "choice3" : "Apolo",
            "choice4" : "Hades",
            "answer" : "1"
        },
        "question3" : {
            "question" : "How old is Hindoeism the oldest religion in the world?",
            "choice1" : "5000 years",
            "choice2" : "10 000 years",
            "choice3" : "30 000 years",
            "choice4" : "50 000 years",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question4" : {
            "question" : "What flower is symbolised for WW1?",
            "choice1" : "Tulip",
            "choice2" : "Rose",
            "choice3" : "Poppy",
            "choice4" : "Narcissus",
            "answer" : "3"
        }
    },
    
    "Category2" : {
          "question0" : {
            "question" : "What is Scientology?",
            "choice1" : " A business",
            "choice2" : "A religion",
            "choice3" : "Both",
            "choice4" : "None of the above",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question1" : {
            "question" : "Which country is the current dominant superpower in the world?",
            "choice1" : "China",
            "choice2" : "Japan",
            "choice3" : "Russia",
            "choice4" : "USA",
            "answer" : "4"
        },
        "question2" : {
            "question" : "Where did the Olympics tradition originate from?",
            "choice1" : "medieval China",
            "choice2" : "Colonial North America",
            "choice3" : "ancient classical Greece",
            "choice4" : "East Roman empire",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question3" : {
            "question" : "Which three religions pray for the same god?",
            "choice1" : "Judaism, Christianity, and Islam",
            "choice2" : "Hindoeism, Boedism, Atheism",
            "choice3" : "Shintoism, Christianity, Islam",
            "choice4" : "Judaism, Christianity Hindoeism",
            "answer" : "1"
        },
        "question4" : {
            "question" : "When was the end of the world supposed to be?",
            "choice1" : "2020",
            "choice2" : "2000",
            "choice3" : "2050",
            "choice4" : "2012",
            "answer" : "4"
        }
    },
    
    "Category3" : {
        "question0" : {
            "question" : "What is Uranus?",
            "choice1" : " a part of an organ",
            "choice2" : "a planet",
            "choice3" : "a moon",
            "choice4" : "a star",
            "answer" : "2"
        },
        "question1" : {
            "question" : "What does a star do when it gets to big?",
            "choice1" : "explodes, nothing else",
            "choice2" : "implodes",
            "choice3" : "explodes either becomes a black hole, a neutron star or a white star",
            "choice4" : "it becomes sad... :(",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question2" : {
            "question" : "What is the moon made out of?",
            "choice1" : "Blue cheese",
            "choice2" : "Solid and semi solid rock",
            "choice3" : "Green cheese",
            "choice4" : "its a hoax",
            "answer" : "2"
        },
        "question3" : {
            "question" : "Which country invented rockets?",
            "choice1" : "The British",
            "choice2" : "Sovjets",
            "choice3" : "germans",
            "choice4" : "Americans",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question4" : {
            "question" : "How many states does the USA have?",
            "choice1" : "45",
            "choice2" : "52",
            "choice3" : "50",
            "choice4" : "56",
            "answer" : "3"
        }
    },
    
    "Category4" : { 
        "question0" : {
            "question" : "Where did the Corona virus originate from?",
            "choice1" : " Siberia, Russia",
            "choice2" : "Wohan, China",
            "choice3" : "North Carolina, USA",
            "choice4" : "Cape Town, South Africa",
            "answer" : "2"
        },
        "question1" : {
            "question" : "how does the corona virus go from person to person?",
            "choice1" : "its a STD like AIDS",
            "choice2" : "its a hoax like climate change",
            "choice3" : "stock exchange",
            "choice4" : "by touch, also transmitted through surfaces, and can temporary go through the air using droplets ",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question2" : {
            "question" : "What are essentials for quarantining in the Pandemic of 2020?",
            "choice1" : "Toiletpaper, is love, is life...",
            "choice2" : "Masks, alcoholic sanitizers",
            "choice3" : "Soap, no human touching, self-isolate",
            "choice4" : "normal routine",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question3" : {
            "question" : "How deadly is the covid-19 virus?",
            "choice1" : "10% death rate",
            "choice2" : "20% death rate",
            "choice3" : " 2-5% death rate",
            "choice4" : "35% death rate",
            "answer" : "3"
        },
        "question4" : {
            "question" : "How are the stocks doing?",
            "choice1" : "reasonably good",
            "choice2" : "really bad worse then the 2008 recession",
            "choice3" : "Not great but not bad either",
            "choice4" : "worse then the 1928 recession which was one of the causes for ww2",
            "answer" : "2"
        }
    }    
}
